Take a look at this
That's pretty interesting
Sir, this is from the Qianlong period
I bought this off a descendant
of the Yehenara clan.
If you like it,
I'll sell it to you cheap.
Dad, these are all fake.
No, no, no.
I'm scoring a bargain here.
Yeah.
You said it's from the Qianlong period,
But this glaze looks way too new.
If it truly is from the Qianlong period,
would the glaze flake off with a scratch?
Well, with the passage of time,
it tends to do that.
This jade transmits light unevenly,
and there are bubbles inside.
Ancient jade pendants were hand-polished.
How could there be bubbles?
All right, all right, enough.
I'm not selling it. I'm not selling it.
Put it down.
Not for sale.
Give it to me, give it to me.
You little punk.
When'd you learn that skill?
I don't know either.
It just came out before I could think.
See if anything here is worth money.
Fake.
This one's fake too.
And this one.
These are all fake.
All fake.
What about my copper coins?
CEO of Sky Roc Entertainment, Zhu Zipeng,
is past the Bronze Sparrow Club incident,
and is publicly preparing a new shoot.
I went to finish that bastard off.
You went to finish him off?
You couldn't even get near him,
and you got hauled off to the Police.
So we just let him get away with it?
You can't take down Zhu Zipeng.
Leave it to me.
You...
You said before
that I owed your sister.
I absolutely hate owing anyone anything.
I've got an important business meeting.
A project worth hundreds of millions.
It's all pocket change.
I'll take you to a movie after this.
Miss Zhu.
I didn't expect you to be so beautiful.
Then I'll get straight to the point.
There's something you should know
that I need to make clear in advance.
As for me,
my one flaw is I attract too many women.
You need to be obedient.
Jealousy is a huge taboo for a wife.
You're that confident
that I'll definitely marry you?
If you don't marry into our family,
my dad won't fund Sky Roc Entertainment.
Isn't your family counting on
trading you for that money?
She doesn't have to marry.
I'll invest.
And who the hell are you?
Get out of here.
Sheng Yuanzhou, from Prosperity Group.
Young Master Sheng from Prosperity Group.
My apologies, my apologies.
Let's go.
Let him cool off here by himself.
Oh, right.
Tell your dad for me,
I don't care about your family's money,
or you.
Mr. Sheng, thank you for today.
If you hadn't been there,
I wouldn't have known what to do.
My parents always say
a married daughter is like spilled water.
Before I'm married off, they always want
to squeeze some value out of me.
Thank you so much for today.
Honestly, even if I hadn't come,
you could've handled him.
Then why did you
come to my rescue again today?
Because I don't want to wait anymore.
I'll be blunt.
I'm actually here to lend you a hand.
I looked into it.
The major projects that turned
Sky Roc Entertainment into a
leading entertainment company
were all personally led by you.
But your parents have son preference,
In the end, your family's assets
can only go to Zhu Zipeng.
You're just a pawn in a Marriage alliance.
No matter how they treat me,
they're still my family.
We're bound by blood.
Stabbing family in the back
isn't something I can do.
Is that so?
Then why did you upload
that rainy-day secret video online?
Don't look so shocked.
As Prosperity Group's heir,
I at least have that much capability.
You posted that secret video online
not to hurt me,
but to use me
to dig up Zhang Xiaoyu's death again.
But digging it up again,
what good does it do you?
I thought it over and finally realized,
you're after the real killer, Zhu Zipeng.
So this is what you meant by
not stabbing family in the back, huh?
Even if I want to bring my brother down,
then, Young Master Sheng,
why would you help me?
You know the Bronze Sparrow Club incident.
He crossed me,
so I'm definitely not letting him off.
Young Master Sheng, can you dance?
Interested in being my dance partner?
The venue is Bronze Sparrow Club.
My brother has a secret computer.
It contains years' worth of videos
of him using Bronze Sparrow Club
to conduct sexual bribery.
Behind the booth is his private room.
The computer should be in the safe.
In a bit, I'll handle
distracting the door guards for you.
The rest depends on your skills.
I came prepared too.
Who is this?
Sis, your new pet?
Yeah.
Even more handsome than you.
Handsome or not...
we'll only know once he takes it off.
What's the fun in revealing it so soon?
So protective.
Don't tell me it's because of him
that you ruined the blind date
Mom set up for you?
I'm telling you,
once a woman hits thirty,
she's past her prime.
I think Sis is in her prime.
And incredibly irresistible.
There's no place for a Simp to speak here.
Young Master Zhu is only half right.
I don't just lick.
I also bite.
Wanna try it, Young Master Zhu?
You have a death wish!
I'd hate for you to bite someone else.
Forget it.
I'm done being the third wheel here.
But I'm warning you,
you'll have to give Mom an explanation
sooner or later.
Mind your own business.
I'm leaving.
I look forward to your performance later.
This bastard.
I smelled a stench.
Turns out a rat snuck in.
Get him!
Somebody!
Somebody, come!
Someone, help!
Forget people.
Even a god couldn't save you.
Because I'm executing divine justice.
Spare me!
This time...
...let's see how you escape.
Sky Roc Entertainment's CEO, Zhu Zipeng,
was arrested by the Police for charges
like tax evasion and illegal fundraising.
Investigations found that the
Prosperity Group worker who killed herself
was also assaulted by Zhu Zipeng.
Sky Roc Entertainment stock price plunged.
falling as much as 10 percent that day.
Prosperity Group's stock price
has returned to pre-scandal levels.
Experts state that
more accurate forecasts come next week.
In a few days, Sky Roc Entertainment
will hit limit down for consecutive days.
Then in a few more days,
we can start buying it at a low price.
Despite a small setback,
you still did a pretty good job.
You've finally shown some growth.
Thank you for the praise, Father.
I hope you keep up this momentum,
so I can consider
making you the Sheng family's heir.
I'll keep working hard.
Also,
take Lin Siqi to try her engagement dress.
Your marriage
needs to be put on the agenda.
Yes, Father.
Sheng Shizhong didn't let Sheng Yuanzhou
become Prosperity Group's heir.
Why?
He's his only biological son.